Guide to the Time Inc. Time Research Center Files: Subject Files MS 3009-RG 13.Series III
New-York Historical Society
- Series III. Subject Files, 1926-2000; 774 Linear feet (774 boxes)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Mississippi, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 22)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Missouri, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 23)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Nebraska, 1977 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: New Jersey, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 25)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: New York (City), 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 26)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: New York (State), 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 27)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: North Carolina, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 28)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Ohio, 1977-1984 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 29)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Oklahoma, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Pennsylvania, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: South Carolina, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Tennessee, 1979-1986 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Texas, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Virginia, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 35)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Washington, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 36)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Public schools: State: Wisconsin, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 37)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Universities and colleges, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2155, Folder 38-45)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Universities and colleges, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 1-8)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Education: Universities and colleges: Fraternities and sororities, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 9)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Jury service, 1985-1992 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 10)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Hospitals and medicine, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Insurance, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Labor, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 13-25)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Law, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 26)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Law: Lawyers, 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 27)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Legislation, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 28)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Municipal services, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 29)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Police, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 30-34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Politics, 1985-1993 (Offsite-box 2156, Folder 35-36)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Politics, 1979-1984 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 1-2)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Press, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 3)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Prisons, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 4)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Public places, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 5)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Radio broadcasting, 1989 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 6)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Residences, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 7-23)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Scottsboro Case, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Show business, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 25)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Sports, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 26-30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Television, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Transportation, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: Unions, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Discrimination: White backlash, 1978-1991 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 1-12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education: Black private schools, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education: Black universities and colleges, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 14-29)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education: Freedom schools, 1978 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education: Scholarships, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Education: Tutors and tutoring, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Foreign relations, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Government relations, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2158, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Gullahs, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 1)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: History, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 2-11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Inter-black relations, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Leadership, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2159, Folder 13-27)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Leadership, 1977-1978 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 1-2)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Migration, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 3)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Militancy, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 4)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: News coverage, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 5)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Passing, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 6)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Politics, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2160, Folder 7-15)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Politics, 1977-1985 (Offsite-box 2161, Folder 1-13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Politics: National Black Political Convention, 1979-1990 (Offsite-box 2161, Folder 14)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Polls, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 1)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Population statistics, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 2)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Preferential treatment, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 3)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Professions, 1981-1991 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 4)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Publications, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 5)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Records (documents), 1984-1986 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 6)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Records (superlatives), 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 7)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Regions, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 8)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Regions: South, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 9-11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Reparations, 1987-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Research, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots, 1980-1991 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 14)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: Investigations, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 15)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: A-W, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 16)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Alabama: Birmingham, 1978-1988 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 17)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: California: A-W, 1992-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 18)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: California: Los Angeles, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2162, Folder 19-24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Florida: A-Z, 1980-1984 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 1)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Florida: Miami, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 2-4)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Georgia: A-Z, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 5)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Illinois: A-Z, 1982 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 6)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Illinois: Chicago, 1977-1990 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 7)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Kansas, 1980 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 8)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Maryland: Baltimore, 1979 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 9)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Michigan: Detroit, 1980-1982 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 10)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: New Jersey, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: New Jersey: Newark, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: New York (City), 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1980 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 14)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Riots: State: Tennessee: Chattanooga, 1980 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 15)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Shows, 1963-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 16)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 17)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama: A-Z, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 18-19)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama: Birmingham, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 20)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama: Mobile, 1981-1986 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 21)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama: Montgomery, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 22)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Alabama: Selma, 1983-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 23)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Arizona, 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Arkansas, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 25)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Arkansas: Little Rock, 1981-1983 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 26)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: California, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 27)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: California: Los Angeles, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 28)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: California: Oakland, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 29)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Colorado, 1981-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Connecticut, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Delaware, 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: District of Columbia, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Florida, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Florida: A-Z, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 35)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Florida: Miami, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 36)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 37)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia: A-Z, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 2163, Folder 38)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia: Atlanta, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 1)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Georgia: Savannah, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 2)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Idaho, 1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 3)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Illinois, 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 4)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Illinois: A-Z, 1977-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 5)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Illinois: Chicago, 1973-1992 (Offsite-box 1764, Folder 6-7)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Illinois: Cicero, 1982-1986 (Offsite-box 2157, Folder 8)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Indiana, 1984-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 9)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Iowa, 1984-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 10)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Kansas, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Kentucky, 1988-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Louisiana, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Louisiana: New Orleans, 1982-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 14)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maine, 1987-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 15)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maryland, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 16)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maryland: A-Z, 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 17)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Maryland: Baltimore, 1983-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 18)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Massachusetts, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 19)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Massachusetts: Boston, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 20)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Michigan, 1978-1990 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 21)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Michigan: A-Z, 1985-1986 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 22)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Michigan: Detroit, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 23)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Minnesota, 1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Mississippi, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 25-26)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Mississippi: A-Z, 1982-1990 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 27-30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Mississippi: Jackson, 1981 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Mississippi: Mississippi Freedom Summer Project, 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Missouri, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Missouri: Kansas City, 1979-1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Missouri: St. Louis, 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 35)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Montana, 1990-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 36)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Nebraska, 1980-1990 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 37)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Nevada, 1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 38)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New Hampshire, 1991 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 39)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New Jersey, 1979-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 40)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New Jersey: Newark, 1986-1992 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 41)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York (City), 1989-1993 (Offsite-box 2164, Folder 42-46)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York (City), 1977-1988 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 1-6)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York (City): Brooklyn, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 7)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York (City): Harlem, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 8)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: New York (State), 1982-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 9)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: North Carolina, 1980-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 10)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: North Carolina: A-Z, 1981-1990 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 11)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: North Carolina: Greensboro, 1990 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 12)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Ohio: A-Z, 1978-1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 13)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Ohio: Cincinatti, 1984-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 14)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Ohio: Cleveland, 1987-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 15)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Oklahoma, 1977-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 16)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Oregon, 1985 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 17)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Pennsylvania, 1986-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 18)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Pennsylvania: Philadelphia, 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 19)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Rhode Island, 1988 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 20)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: South Carolina, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 21)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Tennessee, 1977-1991 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 22)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Tennessee: A-Z, 1983-1986 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 23)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Tennessee: Memphis, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 24)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Texas, 1981-1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 25)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Texas: A-Z, 1980-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 26-27)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Texas: Houston, 1978-1991 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 28)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Utah, 1978-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 29)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Vermont, 1987 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 30)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Virginia, 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 31)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Virginia: A-Z, 1978-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 32)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Virginia: Richmond, 1977-1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 33)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Washington, 1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 34)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: West Virginia, 1988 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 35)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Wisconsin, 1979-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 36)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: State: Wisconsin: Milwaukee, 1981-1992 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 37)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Suburban "blacks" [African Americans], 1979-1989 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 38)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Urban "blacks" [African Americans], 1981-1993 (Offsite-box 2165, Folder 39-40)
  - United States: Population: "Blacks" [African Americans]: Urban "blacks" [African Americans], 1977-1980 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 1-2)
  - United States: Population: British, 1976-1993 (Offsite-box 2228, Folder 3)